A Guide to the Margaret (Peggy) McGrath Rockefeller personal papers FA410
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Accession 2010:057 - East 65th Street, 1946-1996; 1; 33.92 Cubic Feet 58 standard document boxes, 1 oversized flat box, and 7 record storage boxes
  - General Correspondence (East 65th Street), 1946-1996; 1; 15.7 Cubic Feet
    - Kaiser, Mr. and Mrs. Walter (Neva), 1968-1985 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Kane, Mrs. Keith (Amanda), 1959-1973 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Kanzler, Clay, 1988-1989 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Karol, Mr. and Mrs. John (Ann), 1972-1980 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Keidel, Mr. and Mrs. Albert ("Bob")(Justine), 1955-1996 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Keillor, Garrison, 1988-1990 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Kelam, Mr. and Mrs. Arthur (Nan), 1964-1995 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Kellner, Mr. and Mrs. Paul (Clara), 1980-1996 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Kendall, Mr. and Mrs. Donald (Bim), 1988 July-November (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Kennan, Mr. and Mrs. Christopher (Domi), 1986-1994 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Kennan, George, 1985-1992 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Kennan, Libet, 1988-1992 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Kennedy, President and Mrs. John F. (Jacqueline), 1961 May 05 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Kert, Bernice, 1986-1993 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Killam, Dorothy, 1973-1990 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Kimball, Mr. and Mrs. Richard (Hopeton), 1986-1992 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Kirk, Mr. and Mrs. William, 1970-1973 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Kissinger, Dr. and Mrs. Henry (Nancy), 1978-1992 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Klabin, Mr. and Mrs. Israel (Lina)(Stella - daughter), 1963-1979 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Kluge, Mr. and Mrs. John (Patricia), 1985-1991 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Knetge, Mr. and Mrs. Greg (Sara), 1992-1993 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Knight, Amb. and Mrs. Ridgway (Christine), 1977-1986 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Kohr, Mr. and Mrs. Dale, 1983-1984 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Kruger, Mr. and Mrs. George (Leta), 1973-1995 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Kuhl, Honorable John, 1990-1991 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Kusserow, Paul, 1992-1995 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - "K" Miscellaneous, 1952-1995 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Lebrecque, Mr. and Mrs. Thomas (Sheila), 1989-1995 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Lampen, Mr. and Mrs. Rick (Vicky) (Hoyt - son), 1989-1994 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Lahita, Dr. Robert, 1987-1994 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Lapine, James, 1985-1987 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Laszlo, Dr. Andor, 1973 February-March (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Lauder, Estee, 1984-1989 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Lawton, Peter, 1984-1985 (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - Leahy, Jekla, 1975-1995 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Lee, Mr. and Mrs. Benjamin (Flora), 1972 April-October (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Leede, Mr. and Mrs. Edward (Margaret) (Katie - daughter), 1986-1995 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Leisenring, Mr. and Mrs. Edward (Julie), 1989-1995 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Lindsay, Mr. and Mrs. Donald (Andrea), 1974 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Lindsay, Mr. and Mrs. George (Mary), 1975-1995 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Lindstrom, Carl, 1975-1995 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Lloyd, Vidy, 1992-1995 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Loder, James, 1954-1976 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Long, Richard, 1979-1987 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Longworth, Charles ("Chuck"), 1986-1992 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Lord, Phillipa, 1995 January-October (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Lord, Hon. and Mrs. Winston (Bette), 1985-1996 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Loudon, John H., 1975-1995 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Louria, Eva ("Aunt"), 1993 October-November (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Low, Mr. and Mrs. Martin (Alice), 1976-1978 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Lueddeke, Mr. and Mrs. Edward (Patricia), 1990-1996 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Lunt, Mr. and Mrs. Clifton ("Cliff")(Ella), 1973-1980 (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - "L" Miscellaneous, 1956-1995 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - Macalister, Madeline, Geoff and Helen, 1982-1994 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - MacDonald, Lady and Lord, Penelope and Nigel, 1994-1995 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - MacDuffie, Malcom ("Mac"), 1973-1976 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - MacLeish, Mr. and Mrs. Archibald (Ada), 1961-1974 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Macleod, Charlotte, 1967-1972 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Macomber, Mr. and Mrs. John (Caroline), 1978-1986 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Malone, Mr. and Mrs. Adrian (Joan), 1963-1996 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Marquand, Timothy, 1972-1990 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Marshak, Robert, 1984-1987 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Marshall, General G.C., and Katherine, 1958 January-November (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Martin, William McChesney, Jr., 1986-1987 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Marx, Louis, 1969-1974 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Mathers, Mr. and Mrs. William (Myra), 1955-1995 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Matheson, Finlay B. (Bixie), 1995 August-September (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Matheson, Mr. and Mrs. Finlay L. (Cree), 1960-1994 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Mathews, G.H. ("Red"), 1964-1995 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Mathieson, Mr. and Mrs. Andrew ("Drew")(Helen), 1990 January-August (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Matteson, Stephanie, 1983-1993 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Mattingly, Jim, 1973-1975 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Maxwell, William ("Bill"), 1992 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Maze, Mr. and Mrs. Paul (Etienne), 1952-1985 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - McCall, Jeana, 1984-1986 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - McClure, Mr. and Mrs. Don and Eileen, 1972 January-February (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - McCormack, Elizabeth, 1988-1995 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - McCuttcheon, Mrs. Edward (Carol), 1977-1980 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - McGibbon, Mildred "Millie", 1988-1994 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - McGrath, Eileen, 1954-1992 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - McGrath, Mr. and Mrs. Gordon (Grace), 1946-1992 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - McGrath, Joan, 1971-1988 (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - McGrath, Mr. and Mrs. Sims (Pauline), 1954-1995 (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - McNamara, Mr. and Mrs. Robert (Margy), 1972-1980 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Meyer, Mr. and Mrs. Andre (Belle), 1965-1978 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Meyer, Janice, 1976-1978 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Milbury, Mr. and Mrs. Morley (Sandy), 1988-1993 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Millard, Mr. and Mrs. Malcolm ("Mac")(Joanne), 1946-1993 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Miller, Dorothy C., 1975 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Miller, Mr. and Mrs. Leigh (Lynden), 1989-1995 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Miller, Ronald G. ("Ron"), 1986-1995 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Milliken, Roger, Gerrish, Nita, Phoebe, 1968-1995 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Moberg, Robert, 1991-1995 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Moore, Mr. and Mrs. Anthony ("Tony")(Phyllis), 1978-1992 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Moore, Fiona, 1979-1995 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Morgan, Mr. and Mrs. Thomas (Mary), 1985-1995 (Box 21, Folder 13)
      Conditions Governing Access
      Restricted from scholarly access – Documents the activities of a living Rockefeller family member.
    - Morita, Mr. and Mrs. Akio (Yoshiko), 1992-1994 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Morris, Ms. Jan, 1974-1985 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Morris, Mr. and Mrs. Paul (Nicole), 1988-1994 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Moyers, Bill, 1988-1989 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Moynihan, The Honorable and Mrs. Daniel Patrick (Elizabeth), 1974-1994 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Murphy, Mrs. James (Vicky), 1994 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Murphy, Mr. and Mrs. Russell (Eleanor), 1978-1995 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - "M" Miscellaneous, 1950-1969 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - "M" Miscellaneous, 1970-1979 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - "M" Miscellaneous, 1980-1989 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - "M" Miscellaneous, 1990-1995 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - "M" Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Nakhosteen, Joseph, 1972-1996 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Natkin, Mr. and Mrs. Robert (Judy), 1971-1989 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Neeson, Jeanne M., 1989 January (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Neilson, Mr. and Mrs. Harry R. Jr. (Janeche), 1977-1995 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Neubert, Mrs. Guenter (Edith), 1971 July (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Nichols, Mrs. Charles W. (Peggy), 1972-1986 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Nickerson, Mr. and Mrs. Albert (Elizabeth), 1978-1995 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Nields Colonna, Elizabeth, 1992-1996 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Nields, Mrs. John W. (Lila), 1975-1979 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Nixon, President Richard M. and Mrs. Nixon (Pat), 1980 June 4 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Nybo, Greta, 1977-1995 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - "N" Miscellaneous, 1958-1995 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - O'Brien, Mr. and Mrs. Donal C., Jr. (Katie), 1972-1996 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Okada, Mrs. and Mrs. Kenzo (Kimi), 1974-1984 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Oltmer, Dieter, 1978-1980 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - O'Neal, Dianne, 1992-1994 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - O'Neill, Mr. and Mrs. George (Abby), 1974-1996 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - O'Neill, Laura, 1975-1980 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Owens, Harry L., 1980-1989 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Owings, Mr. and Mrs. Nathaniel (Margaret), 1951-1989 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - "O" Miscellaneous, 1958-1995 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Packer, Mr. and Mrs. Kerry (Rosie), 1987-1990 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Paley, Mr. and Mrs. William (Babs), 1969-1985 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Pao, Mr. and Mrs. Y.K. (Doreen), 1977-1986 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Pappalardo, Mr. and Mrs. Conrado (Marita), 1986-1995 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Paranhos, Lina Caldaz, 1972-1990 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Parilla, Alicia, 1991-1994 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Parker, Rita, 1960-1973 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Parsons, Douglas V. N., 1978-1979 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Passauer-McCallister, Mrs. W. D. (Judy), 1984-1996 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Patterson, David, 1975-1988 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Patterson, Mrs. and Mrs. David C. (Ann H.), 1957-1968 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Peer, Gerard, 1973 October-November (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Peet, Mr. and Mrs. Robert I. (Helene), 1980-1994 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Perkins, Mr. and Mrs. James. A. (Ruth), 1974 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Perkins, Mr. and Mrs. Malcolm D. (Sheila), 1965 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Petschek, Stephen R., 1972-1979 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Peterson, Peter G., 1979-1991 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Pew, Mr. and Mrs. R. Anderson (Joanie), 1978 May-August (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Phelan, Mr. and Mrs. James (Sondra), 1980-1995 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Phillips, Mrs. James C., Jr. (Florence - "Flossie"), 1964-1995 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Pillsbury, Mr. and Mrs. Donaldson (Marnie), 1990-1996 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Piancone, Mr. and Mrs. Louis (Teri Kaufman), 1994-1995 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Pigot, Mrs. J.S.G. (Coco), 1974-1977 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Pinto-Coelho, Durate, 1986-1987 (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - Place, Angela Moore, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - Place, Mr. and Mrs. David E. (Penelope), 1975-1991 (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - Plunkett, Mr. and Mrs. Jake (Louise), 1984-1992 (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - Potter, Jeffrey, 1991 April-May (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - Praeger, Mrs. C.W. (Lillian), 1984 August-October (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - Pulsifer, Mrs. J.T. (Susan), 1977 December (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - Purdum, Ralph Stanley, 1965-1978 (Box 23, Folder 31)
    - Pusey, Mr. and Mrs. Nathan (Anne), 1957-1994 (Box 23, Folder 32)
    - Putnam, Mr. and Mrs. George (Barbie), 1988 March-June (Box 23, Folder 33)
    - "P" Miscellaneous, 1970-1996 (Box 23, Folder 34)
    - Quattrone, Mr. David and Family, 1972-1974 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Quesada, Peter W., 1988-1995 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - "Q" Miscellaneous, 1995 December 30 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Ralston, Peter, 1987-1988 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Random House, 1991 June-July (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Rappleyea, Clarence D., Jr., 1984-1985 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Rashid, Abdul, 1974-1980 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Rea, Mary, 1974-1994 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Reed, Mr. and Mrs. Joseph V. (Mimi), 1970-1995 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Reston, Mrs. James (Sally), 1973 June-July (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Rickett, Harold "Rick", 1967-1973 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Rigg, Mrs. Allen (Joan), 1975-1979 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Ripley, Mrs. Dillon, 1984-1987 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Roberts, Ann R., 1977-1985 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Rockefeller, John D. IV (Sharon), 1956-1995 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Rockefeller, Mr. and Mrs. John D. 3rd (Blanchette), 1962-1992 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Rockefeller, Mr. and Mrs. Laurance (Mary), 1970-1996 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Rockefeller, Margaret McGrath ("Peggy"), 1983-1995 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Rockefeller, Gov. and Mrs. Nelson (Happy), 1959-1984 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Rockefeller, Mr. and Mrs. Rodman (Sascha), 1984-1996 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Rockefeller, Steven C. [Restricted], 1968-1989 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Rockefeller, Sydney Roberts, 1977-1995 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Rockefeller, Mrs. Mary C. (Tod), 1962-1990 (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Rockefeller, Winthrop, 1972-1980 (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Rockefeller Family (Extended) Miscellaneous, 1957-1993 (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Rockwell, Mr. and Mrs. Charles E. (Barbara), 1965-1987 (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Rohm, Mrs. J. E. (Susan), 1986-1996 (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Roosevelt, Mrs. Theodore III (Anne), 1985-1992 (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - Roosevelt, Mrs. and Mrs. Archibald (Lucky and Archie), 1977-1985 (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - Rorimer, Mrs. James (Kay), 1973-1976 (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - Rothschild, Mr. Edmond de, 1973-1978 (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - Rowan, Dina, 1980 February-April (Box 24, Folder 32)
    - Roy, S.K. (Sunil), 1964-1977 (Box 24, Folder 33)
    - Ruebhausen, Mr. and Mrs. Oscar (Zelia), 1960-1994 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Russell, Mr. and Mrs. Diarmuid (Rosie), 1956-1986 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Russell, William, 1972-1992 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - "R" Miscellaneous, 1958-1994 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Sage, Dewitt L., 1994 August-October (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Salazar, Mr. and Mrs. Felix, 1976-1985 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Salisbury, Marchioness (Momi), 1989 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Salles, Mr. and Mrs. Walther (Moreira), 1988-1993 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Salomon, Richard, 1973-1996 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Santo Domingo, Mr. and Mrs. Julio Mario, 1992-1995 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - al-Saud-al-Sabah, Her Highness Sheikha Badriah, 1978 May-September (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Sawyer, Mr. and Mrs. George (Jennie), 1984-1996 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Schieffelin, Mrs. William Jay (Annette), 1972-1974 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Schiffer, Mr. and Mrs. Kenneth (Bay), 1965-1994 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Schmidt, Mr. and Mrs. Benno (Nancy), 1972-1983 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Schneeweis, Mr. and Mrs. Michael (Joan), 1991-1992 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Schram, Earl, Jr., 1984-1994 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Scott, Leslie N., 1973-1990 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Scranton, Mr. and Mrs. William (Mary), 1980-1994 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Seabrook, Mr. and Mrs. John (Liz), 1984-1995 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Segal, Martin F., 1985 November (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Seitz, Mr. and Mrs. Frederick (Betty), 1974 June (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Serkin, Irene, 1960 October-December (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Sessler, Annunciata, 1993-1995 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Shapiro, Daniel, 1994-1996 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Shidatsu, Yasushi, 1986 April-May (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Sichel, Mrs. Peter (Stella), 1985-1990 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Sidamo-Eristoff, Mr. and Mrs. Constantine "Connie" (Anne), 1985 July (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Silverman, Mrs. William (Marilyn), 1973-1979 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Slocum,Mr. and Mrs. John (Eileen), 1985-1991 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Simpson, Mr. and Mrs. William "Kelly" (Marilyn), 1980-1985 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Smalley, Patricia ("Trix"), 1985-1990 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Smith, Alice, 1984 March-April (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Smith, Dennis, 1973-1977 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Sprague-Smith, Mr. and Mrs. Carleton (Elizabeth), 1978-1983 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Stankard, Mrs. Francis X. (Elsa), 1978-1979 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Stanley, Mrs. Wilder (Gerry), 1986-1987 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Staples, Mr. and Mrs. Milton (Melita), 1974-1978 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Stein, Jean, 1988-1995 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Stein, Martin H., 1988-1992 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Stevenson, Mrs. John R. (Ruth), 1962-1994 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Stillman, Chauncey, 1975-1988 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Straus, Mr. and Mrs. Donald (Beth) (Sara "Sally" - daughter), 1964-1995 (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - Straus, Mrs. and Mrs. Robert (Sheryl), 1985-1990 (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - Strawbridge, David A., 1974-1992 (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - Strong, Mr. and Mrs. Corrin Peter (Alice), 1972-1974 (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - Stuart, Robert D., Jr., 1993 October-November (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - Sulzberger, Mr. and Mrs. Arthur Hays (Iphigene), 1967-1975 (Box 26, Folder 29)
    - Sulzberger, Mr. and Mrs. Arthur O. "Punch" (Carol), 1985-1990 (Box 26, Folder 30)
    - Sununu, Mrs. John (Nancy), 1990 April (Box 26, Folder 31)
    - Swanzey, Mr. and Mrs. Thomas (Florence), 1973-1984 (Box 26, Folder 32)
    - Swing, John Temple, 1975-1978 (Box 26, Folder 33)
    - Swinney, H.J., 1968-1969 (Box 26, Folder 34)
    - "S" Miscellaneous, 1956-1996 (Box 26, Folder 35)
    - Talbot, Mrs. Phillips (Mildred), 1979 April (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Tarnoff, Mr. and Mrs. Peter (Martha), 1986-1988 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Tata, J.E.H. ("Jeh"), 1977-1986 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Taylor, Mr. and Mrs. Dean (Gloria), 1980-1987 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Taylor, George D., Jr., 1985-1988 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Thomas, Joseph B., IV, 1976-1977 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Thompson, Estelle, 1974 February-June (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Thompson, G. David, 1961-1965 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Thorndike, Mrs. Amory (Betty)(John - nephew), 1977-1989 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Thornton, Mr. and Mrs. Charles ("Tex")(Flora), 1980 July-August (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Thurber, Mr. and Mrs. LeGrande ("Lee")(Charlotte - "Sharlie"), 1966-1992 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Tischbein, Heather, 1978-1979 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Tree, Marietta, 1987-1991 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Tully, Alice, Undated (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Tweedsmuir, Lord and Lady (John and Priscilla), 1961-1992 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - "T" Miscellaneous, 1965-1995 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Underhill, Stanley, 1972-1975 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - "U" Miscellaneous, 1973-1990 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Vachtmeister, Countess (Ulla), 1986 February-May (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Vance, Mrs. Cyrus R. (Gay), 1974-1976 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Van der Kamp, Mr. and Mrs. Gerald (Florence), 1971-1980 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Vanderlip, Mr. and Mrs. Frank, Jr. (Eileen McGrath), 1959-1988 (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - van Doormaal, Ina, 1977-1978 (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - van Dorn, Gerald, 1975 August-December (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - Van Hook, George, 1990 July-September (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - Van Poznak, Dr. Alan, 1983-1994 (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - Varnedoe, Kirk, 1990-1991 (Box 27, Folder 27)
    - Verey, Mrs. David (Rosemary), 1984-1985 (Box 27, Folder 28)
    - Verrill, James Trundy, 1977 September-October (Box 27, Folder 29)
    - Victor, Mrs. Alexander (Anna Glen), 1976-1994 (Box 27, Folder 30)
    - Villares, Mr. and Mrs. Paulo (Helena), 1984-1989 (Box 27, Folder 31)
    - Visceglia, Diego, 1987 February (Box 27, Folder 32)
    - Voell, Mr. and Mrs. Richard (Ginny), 1984-1986 (Box 27, Folder 33)
    - Volcker, Paul A., 1993-1994 (Box 27, Folder 34)
    - Voorhees, Mr. and Mrs. Stan ("Brokie")(Dotty), 1989-1992 (Box 27, Folder 35)
    - "V" Miscellaneous, 1954-1995 (Box 27, Folder 36)
    - Walk, Mrs. Everett (Sybil), 1973-1990 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Walker, David, 1955-1956 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Wallenberg, Marc, 1972 September 29 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Waller, Mrs. Thomas (Willie), 1976-1978 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Wallis, James T., 1973-1992 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Wallis, Mrs. Phillip (Mims), 1976-1984 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Walls, Mr. and Mrs. Edgar (Nancy), 1973-1995 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Walston, Mr. and Mrs. John (Cheryl), 1991-1993 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Warden, Mr. and Mrs. Timothy (Karin), 1987-1988 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Wardwell, Linnea, 1992-1994 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Watson, Mr. and Mrs. Scott (Vivian), 1974-1989 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Webb, Mr. and Mrs. Grant (Sally), 1991 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Weil, Mr. and Mrs. Peter (Susie), 1986-1995 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Weinberg, Benjamin, 1988-1989 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Weinberger, Mrs. and Mrs. Casper (Jane), 1992 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Weinstock, David, 1990-1995 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Weld, Dr. Francis M. ("Tim"), 1987 December (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Welles, Arnold, 1973-1985 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Welles, Admiral E.R., 1974-1976 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Wellin, Mrs. Keith (Nancy), 1991-1994 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Wheeler, Douglas, 1986-1987 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - Wheelright, Mrs. H. J. (Mary), 1975-1976 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - Whitehead, Mr. and Mrs. John (Nancy Dickerson), 1990-1995 (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - Whiting, Mrs. Margaret, 1977-1980 (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - Whyte, Mrs. D. G. (Dorothy), 1976-1979 (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - Wilke, Mr. and Mrs. John (Margot), 1974-1995 (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - Wilkerson, Eleanor, 1964-1976 (Box 28, Folder 27)
    - Williams, Mrs. Douglas (Priscilla), 1988-1991 (Box 28, Folder 28)
    - Williams, Langbourne, 1955-1992 (Box 28, Folder 29)
    - Willman, Mr. E.T. (Palmer Johnson Inc.), 1972 November (Box 28, Folder 30)
    - Wilson, Mrs. Loretta, 1989-1992 (Box 28, Folder 31)
    - Wing, Wade, Donna, Tori, Cassie, 1989-1996 (Box 28, Folder 32)
    - Winship, Thomas, 1989-1993 (Box 28, Folder 33)
    - Winthrop, Mrs. Nathaniel (Eleanor), 1984-1990 (Box 28, Folder 34)
    - Winthrop, Frederic, Jr., 1985-1989 (Box 28, Folder 35)
    - Wolf, Charles, 1984-1990 (Box 28, Folder 36)
    - Wolf, Mr. and Mrs. Walter ("Billy")(Irene), 1969-1995 (Box 28, Folder 37)
    - Wolfe, James, 1960-1964 (Box 28, Folder 38)
    - Wolfe, James E., 1971-1989 (Box 28, Folder 39)
    - Wolfensohn, Mr. and Mrs. James (Elaine), 1984-1995 (Box 28, Folder 40)
    - Wood, Mr. and Mrs. James (Twink), 1984-1996 (Box 28, Folder 41)
    - Wooley, Mr. and Mrs. John (Dale), 1957-1992 (Box 28, Folder 42)
    - Woolf, Mrs. Harry (Pat), 1986-1987 (Box 28, Folder 43)
    - Wrightsman, Mrs. Charles (Jayne), 1973-1977 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Wyeth, Mr. and Mrs. James (Jamie)(Phyllis), 1981-1992 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Wylie, Andrew, 1989-1990 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Wylie, Mr. and Mrs. Craig (Augie), 1955-1989 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Wylie, Jennifer, 1978 April-June (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - "W" Miscellaneous, 1951-1996 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Yarn, Mrs. Charles (Jane), 1978-1979 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - "Y" Miscellaneous, 1974-1995 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Zuckerman, Mr. and Mrs. Richard (Jessica), 1992-1995 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - "Z" Miscellaneous, 1958-1992 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Copies of correspondence filed chronologically (possibly duplicates), 1977-1990 (Box 30)
  - Topical Files (East 65th Street), 1942-1996; 2; 22 Cubic Feet
    - Personal Files, 1942-1986; 1
      - Chapin's 50th Class Reunion, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 1)
      - Chapin School Alumnae Bulletin, "Class Notes News", 1990-1996 (Box 31, Folder 2)
      - "The Colonial Ancestry of Elizabeth Bordley Belt McGrath 1942-1926" by Francis Sims McGrath (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Cosmopolitan Club (Cattle Speech) and Miscellaneous, 1982 (Box 31, Folder 4)
      - Decorating Correspondence, 1972-1986 (Box 31, Folder 5)
      - French Clothes (sketches and material samples), 1950-1962 (Box 31, Folder 6)
      - Kasetsart University, Bangkok, Thailand - Honorary Doctorate of Sciences (Agriculture) (Box 31, Folder 7)
      - Mr. and Mrs. F. Sims McGrath's 45th Wedding Anniversary Party: June 18, 1955 (Box 31, Folder 8)
      - Passport Photo, 1987 February 23 (Box 31, Folder 9)
      - Pet Dogs: Dandy and Trigvie, 1973-1986 (Box 31, Folder 10)